Hello, my name is Oscar.
I'm an accountant
in Scranton, Pennsylvania
and I am gay.
And I'm here
to tell you that, yes,
it does get better.
When I was younger...
What? What's he doing?
He's searching out
younger gays.
No, it's just a way
to tell young people
no matter how hard
it gets for them
there's a brighter
future ahead.
With you.
No matter how hard
it gets for you...
Kelly, seriously, I...
Just keep chatting.
I'm just checking
my makeup in your webcam.
Do you not own a mirror?
Webcams make me look
the way I look
in my fantasies.
PAM: I know, right?
What is it? You always look
so good in those things.
I'm throwing out
all my mirrors.
Okay, as you can see,
I now have a cool job
at a dynamic workplace.
Being gay
is a celebration of life.
It's a simple...
I'm sorry. I just
can't sit idly by
and have
the gay youth of America
misled by
some reductionist...
I'm not misleading.
...pep talk.
Sexuality is a spectrum.
It's a paradox to think
of any sexual activity
as normal.
It gets better,
but it also gets vastly
more complicated.
Hey, Robert? That guy,
he looks just like you.
Damn it! Kevin. God!
(KEVIN GROANING)
You okay, Robert?
ROBERT: I'm fine.
Put some ice on it.
In any case,
it gets better.
(KEVIN WHIMPERS)
Maybe not much better,
but better.
KEVIN: It hurts.
One, two, three.
DWIGHT: I wanted to give
a nice gift to the tenants
in the building.
At first I thought,
"Muffin basket."
Then I thought,
"What's even more precious
to people than muffins?"
Can you just
smile, please?
I don't want to!
Their own children.
Hey, everybody.
Just a few hours left
for the free family
portrait studio.
Darryl, we'd love to see
little Jada come by.
Angela, why don't you
bring by your little angel?
No, thank you.
Jim, you've got
those two cute kids.
We sure would
love to see them.
I know why you're
doing this, Dwight.
Last week, I may
have gone too far.
I'll explain it quickly.
Basically I found out
where he gets
his clothes dry-cleaned,
custom-ordered
the same suit made
with tear-away Velcro
and you can
fill in the rest.
What?
(LAUGHING)
Damn it, Jim!
Now he's trying
to get me to bring
my children into work.
I think it's fair
to be cautious.
Let me get this straight,
you lost all of it?
All your winnings,
$150,000?
You mean to tell me
no one wanted
an energy drink
for Asian homosexuals?
They did not.
You've got
half-a-million of these?
Well, I've got to try it.
I wouldn't.
Oh, come on.
What's the harm?
Hmm.
What flavor is that?
The coconut's pretty subtle.
Come on, man.
Can you just give us
a yes or a no?
I don't know, man.
You all quit with
a lot of confidence.
I mean, you all
came up in here dancing
and everybody was...
Ooh! Hold on a second.
If I were Val, I would
break up with Brandon.
Then I would date
the hell out of me.
I wouldn't give in
to me too fast,
let me buy myself
some nice dinners
and such.
When I finally did give in,
I would go crazy on myself.
Hi, guys.
How's it going, man?
I'm... I'm good.
Thank you. How are you?
Great, yeah. Good.
Oh, how the mediocre
have fallen.
Oh, God.
Look, I'm not here
to get my old job back.
I had my opportunity,
I blew it.
I'm moving on.
Just wanted to come in here
and literally beg you
for something, anything.
I will sweep the floors,
water the plants.
No, you don't...
Clean the toilets.
I don't need anyone...
Pull the poop
out of the toilets.
Not even a thing.
Just please...
Andy. Andy.
Please give me something.
Why don't you clean
the carpets for today?
Thank you.
Well, you're...
Up you get, then.
Pick yourself up.
There it is.
Thank you.
You don't need to.
I have a delicious secret.
(WHISTLING)
Good, good.
This carpet's overdue
for a good mopping.
Is a mop
the most efficient tool
to use on a carpet?
Yeah, it is, actually.
(GRUNTS) I can't hold
it in any longer.
I am faking this, okay?
Because I convinced
David Wallace
to buy Dunder Mifflin
back from Sabre
and at 3:00 today
he's going to
walk in here
and reinstate me
as manager.
Family picture.
Pam. No.
What? Honey, we talked
about this.
No, we talked about
not bringing them
into Dwight's photo
studio/trap.
Yes, and then we decided
that was crazy.
No, we decided
it was crazy not to
worry about it.
No, we settled
in a much more
rational place,
remember?
No.
We decided that
there's no way Dwight
would harm a child.
But are you 100% sure?
I don't think any of us are.
No, no.
Nope.
But it's free
and we'll keep
our eye on them.
Yes.
Yes, that's...
And we will make sure that
Dwight doesn't do anything...
Okay.
...C-R-A-Z-Y.
Wait. C-R-A-Z...
Great, right up there.
Yeah.
You sit right here,
one time.
There you go.
Okay.
All right, why don't you
just give him to me?
Oh, great. Thank you.
Perfect.
This is great, excuse me.
You ready? There you go.
Okay.
All right, let's do it.
I'll just stand here then.
Yeah, just keep
your eye on Dwight.
Okay, yeah.
Sir, could you
look into the camera?
Let's do it.
Shoot it. Great.
Sir.
Up here.
(WHISTLES)
JIM: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jim, right here,
right here.
Okay. Good.
Oh, so that's it?
That's it.
See, that wasn't so hard.
DWIGHT: Cute kids.
Thanks for coming.
Hello, Erin.
Hello, everybody.
What, why? Hi, honey.
What... How are you doing?
You know,
my office got a call
that they were shooting
family portraits right here.
And if there's one thing
every politician
instinctively understands,
it's a good photo op.
(CHUCKLING)
Okay, you're going to go
through the hallway.
Here's a map.
And if you get lost
just follow the blue line.
Thanks.
Well, well, well,
Senator Lipton. Welcome.
Angela.
Dwight.
Nice to see you.
May I hold him?
Sure.
No. I am going to hold him
because I haven't
seen him all day.
I think that Dwight
is doing this whole thing
to get a sample
of my baby's DNA
to prove he's the father.
Which is impossible.
Because the Senator
is the only man
I've ever been with.
Did you see that?
What do you think
about that? See?
See that ducky?
Okay, hold on
a second, folks.
A few of the baby's hairs
are out of place.
Oh, thank you.
No, no, no.
I like the baby's hair
the way it is.
Really?
This is getting
more and more delicious
by the minute.
(GARGLING)
(COUGHING)
It's go time.
Hey, Nellie.
I made... I made you...
I made you some soup.
Well, I don't
want any soup.
But it's really good.
Oh! Come on, Andy.
Ah.
I know this is going
to be a great payoff.
A delicious moment.
But after you're manager,
some of these images
are going to be
hard to shake.
Well, but it's...
Just calibrate.
Okay? Calibrate.
DWIGHT: Okay, here we go.
Oh, you know what?
I don't want to throw
a wrench into the works,
but I want everything
to be perfect
and the baby's fingernails
are just bothering me.
Uh-uh. Leave us alone.
I guess we're okay
with the fingernails.
Okay, great.
Suit yourself.
(ANGELA COOING)
Although,
aren't those
excess skin cells
in the baby's cheek
distracting to you as well?
Dwight! We're fine.
Oopsie! Did somebody
make a poopsie?
I'm just going
to take him out
and change him
just for a second here.
He defecated.
Ooh!
Oh!
Stinky.
A lot has changed
since you all left, okay?
You're going to have to
jump through some hoops.
And the new foreman is here.
Now, she's one of the best
we've ever known, okay?
So I need you to show her
your utmost respect.
Make sure that
she feels welcome
and at home, okay?
Can you do that?
That's some pretty
blatant complimenting
you're doing there, man.
I don't even talk
to her like that.
VAL: Uh, Brandon.
I would.
You would?
Yeah.
Sounds like you're trying
to hit on my girlfriend.
Calm down. He's not.
Yes, I am.
Just so everyone's
on the same page.
(SCOFFS) So you really
think she's going to
leave a guy who owns
his own restaurant
for a dude who ate
his own restaurant?
Brandon.
Good slam.
BRANDON: Thank you, Biggie.
Good luck to you.
Oh, and have
a burger for me.
Okay, shall we
take a few more?
I think we have
all the shots we need.
Thank you, Dwight.
Okay, here we go.
Yes, here we go.
No, Dwight!
Give me the diaper!
Dwight!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Is this what
you were looking for?
Huh? Huh?
TOBY: Andy, we wanted
to talk to you.
A lot of us are very
concerned about you.
You're dirty,
you stink of booze,
you're limping inexplicably.
I just want you guys
not to worry
because old Andy's
going to be just fine.
No, no, no,
see, this is what
we're talking about.
I mean, what was
that accent?
And last time I checked
you were drunk and now
you're not drunk.
No, unfortunately,
it's true.
He's been a nightmare
and the worst part is
he's been taking it out
on me.
You hit her?
NELLIE: What?
No, no!
That is not the deal.
Calibrate.
He's not hitting me,
but he's been verbally
abusing me.
ANDY: That is
not true, either!
(ALL TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
That's also total...
Everyone please relax.
I think you're going to
like this surprise guest.
Happy birthday to Gabe.
Oh, get out,
Skeleton Man.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
I can refer you to
someone to talk to.
Huh?
I can give you a name.
Hold on.
I'm just going to... Hello?
Hey, what's the scoop?
Are you close?
What?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You have to come now.
Traffic clears.
No, next Friday.
That's not going to work.
Okay, yeah, okay.
Damn it.
Well, this is not
going to be quite as
delicious as I wanted,
but I do have a very
tasty announcement
for you guys.
Not only am I not
a lowly janitor,
I am the regional manager
once again.
Guys, I got
my old job back.
Oh, boy.
Oh, Andy.
I'm not crazy.
I convinced David Wallace
to give me my job back.
David Wallace
hasn't worked here
in years.
Okay, yes,
I see the confusion.
I saw David
at the fundraiser.
He is now
a multi-millionaire
because he sold
his toy vacuum "Suck It"
to the U.S. Military.
Andy, come on, man.
(ALL MURMURING)
I... Okay, I get how
that sounds crazy.
Andy, nobody's calling
you crazy, Andy.
We're your friends, Andy.
Stop saying my name.
No, he's not
making this up.
Thank you, Erin.
Andy tells me about
seeing David Wallace
all the time.
But have you ever
actually seen him yourself?
Oh, my God. Wait.
Erin, come... Come on.
You know I've been
talking to David Wallace.
Do you see David Wallace
in the room right now?
Operation Phoenix is a go.
Just get the car ready.
Okay, you look at me
like you're adoring me
and I'm going to
look at the camera
like I don't even
know you're there.
But I do adore you.
Andrew, it's time
for you to go home.
You're better than this.
Yeah, I know.
Everyone is
better than this.
Because this is
the worst thing
I have ever seen.
Why did they add coconut?
I miss original.
DAVID: Hey.
WOMAN: Hey.
Hey, guys.
ANGELA: Hey!
Hey, guys, long time.
David, what are
you doing here?
Is it true you're
buying the company?
Okay, I guess
the word is out.
Please keep this a secret,
but yes, I've been
talking with Andy.
What? I thought
I heard my name. What?
I'm the new manager?
I'll get to that
in a second, Andy.
But it's...
It is me? Right?
DAVID: Yes,
as we discussed.
ANDY: What?
Oh, my God!
It's very possible...
Probable.
Wow. From janitor
to manager?
Yep.
It's quite
a Cinderella story.
From M-O-P to MVP.
There's an
official announcement.
A few details...
From total loss
to total boss. I mean...
Can we expect
any payroll interruptions?
DAVID: Now that is
a great question, Stanley.
Right now I think
all your operations,
or most of your operations
are pretty much
down in Florida,
so the shift back...
I was so looking
forward to that
and it did not go
as I thought it would.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
So we're not
going to be a part
of Sabre anymore?
Actually nothing
is going to be
a part of Sabre anymore.
Jo Bennett's
planning on liquidating
the rest of the company.
Oof! (LAUGHING)
Wouldn't want to
be a Sabre employee
right about now.
(ROBERT LAUGHING)
I'm actually the CEO.
Ah!
I didn't realize
you were standing there.
Hey, my friend, trust me.
This is for the best.
I never understood
that corporate mess.
Well, okay.
Well, great to meet you.
Likewise, I'm Bob,
Bob Kazamakis.
DAVID: Pleasure.
I'd love to give you
a little rundown
on what I've learned
about this place.
DAVID: That's very
gracious of you, Bob.
I would love that.
Please.
(LAUGHING)
I guess I better
take off these dirty rags
and figure out how to be
a manager of this place.
Perhaps your
year of experience
managing this branch
will come in handy.
Gosh, I hope so.
No! God, Mose. God!
Hi, Angela.
Get out of the car!
Get out!
Where is he? Where is he?
I'm not supposed to say.
Yes, tell me!
Tell me where he is!
Mose! Damn it!
Where did he go?
Mose, get back here!
(SHUTTER CLICKING)
DARRYL: See that smile.
Jump in here.
Come on.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Looks like I might get
my delicious moment
after all.
May I say one thing?
It would be rude of me
not to let you say
whatever's on your mind.
"The quality of mercy
is not strained."
No.
"It dropeth as
the gentle rain from heaven
upon the place beneath."
Do not bring Shakespeare
into this.
How dare you play
the "Bard Card."
"It blesseth he who gives
and he who takes.
"'Tis mightiest
in the mightiest."
I just want
one mother (BLEEP)
delicious moment.
Is that too much to ask?
If I were to
hire you back, if,
what do you think
you would do well?
Special projects manager.
That's my background.
I just go around
doing whatever I want.
All right, you sly bastard,
when can you start?
(SHUTTER CLICKING)
Okay, everyone.
I had a conversation
with Bob
and since I am
going to be CEO now,
there'll be no need for him.
Ouch! That's got to hurt!
But he is going to make
so much money
from the liquidation,
he's going to be
freed up to do
something much
more important.
What?
David has generously
offered to donate
$1,000,000 in matching funds
to a cause
that's very dear to me.
So for the next three years,
I'll be traveling overseas,
concentrating
all of my efforts
on educating, mentoring,
some African,
some Asian, but mainly
Eastern European women.
DAVID: I had no idea
how pervasive
this problem was until
Bob explained it to me.
Oprah Winfrey's
Leadership Academy,
and other schools like it,
while wonderful,
end with high school.
I want to see these girls
right through college.
Especially the gymnasts.
They've lost so many years
of crucial education
to perfecting their bodies.
Muscle groups
the rest of us
can't even fathom.
Gymnasts?
You're going to seek out
uneducated gymnasts?
Yeah. So I'm hoping
to identify some truly
exceptional women
who show great promise.
Well, Andy, it's been fun.
Hmm.
It's been a great year.
DWIGHT: Hello.
Where is it?
They're testing it now.
How long does it take
to get the results?
Seventy-two hours.
You're going to wait here?
Yes.
Dwight, I can't do this.
Dwight!
Hey.
Senator Lipton.
Hey, how are you?
You didn't call.
Um...
Well, the issue
that concerned me...
You know what
this is about.
(SOFTLY) Call.